<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geoscience Blog</title>
    <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Geoscience Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aozweb.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Geoscience Multiverse</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/talk/second-seedling/</guid>
      <description>Panorama     El curso desarrolla desde los conceptos básicos de geodatabase (base de datos geoespacial) para entender la estructura y funcionamiento de base de datos espacial. Además se realiza el análisis estadístico exploratorio de aguas, suelo, rocas y sedimentos de drenaje, así como modelos estadísticos, geoestadísticos y de machine learning para su aplicación en recursos hídricos, geoquímica, hidroquímica, peligros geológicos, rock blasting todo esto enmarcado en la interactividad y desarrollo web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Statical Data Analysis Applied to Geology</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/talk/campfire/</guid>
      <description>I was really excited to gave this talk! Stay tuned for video and slides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Next Project</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/project/penguins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/project/penguins/</guid>
      <description> “Something is going to come soon. So stay fullish, stay hungry.”     — Alonso Otiniano, Ist working on this application [^1]
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Feb 2019 13:38:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>** Contact page don&amp;rsquo;t contain a body, just the front matter above. See form.html in the layouts folder.
Formspree requires a (free) account and new form to be set up. The link is made on the final published url in the field: Restrict to Domain. It is possible to register up to 2 emails free and you can select which one you want the forms to go to within Formspree in the Settings tab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contributors</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/contributors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/contributors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you to all the folks who have contributed both technical and creative skills to this project:
   Ing. Joseps Andrade Choque: (give me all the feedback to understand how works html and web applications)
   Dr. Carlos Benavente: (give me the opportunity to create in geology all that my mind believe)
   Enviromental Base Line: (all the team that believes in my knowledge in geoscience and statistics)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://aozweb.netlify.app/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aozweb.netlify.app/license/</guid>
      <description>My blog posts are released under a Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
